accessorygeeks.com 2012-10-05

# About Us - Free Shipping.

---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
|  |   
  
The Geeks behind the scenes of AccessoryGeeks.com come from various corners of the world with different cultures and backgrounds but the one thing that stands universal between us is our geekdom. Each of us embrace what it means to be a Geek and the values this sub-culture instills. We Geeks enjoy sharing our knowledge and expertise with others as well as deepening our connections with the community and customers alike. Whether it's a WoW raid, Halo war, or an intense discussion about which Superhero has the best gadgets, we've got our bases covered. Hey, we'll even tell you which cell phone case best accents your Friday night outfit. And in case (pun totally intended) you were wondering: Black never goes out of style.

Like Superman or Iron Man, we at AccessoryGeeks.com have a backstory that makes us the company we are today. No, we didn't come from a planet in a galaxy not so far away, but we did stem from the turn of the 21st century when sleek cell phones were still an X-files luxury. 2004 marked our explosion onto the worldwide web and it was with gusto that we took the reins of the internet so we could provide top quality products and service to those in need of cell phone accessories & other electronic device accessories. Still going strong, AccessoryGeeks.com continues to strive to bring the ultimate package in terms of great customer service, quality products, and a promise to uphold the values that make up a Geek.

Being a Geek isn’t just about the latest and greatest in technology. Being a Geek is about being passionate and sharing your knowledge with the world! We’ve been privileged enough to have our vision covered by the likes of CNET, iPhone Life Magazine, CBS News, KFI Radio, the New York Times and Forbes and look forward to sharing our Geeky values with more of the world as well as helping to make it a better place. AccessoryGeeks.com works closely with [Lifehouse Ministry](http://www.lifehouseministryoc.com/), [AADAP](http://www.aadapinc.org/), and the [Hadley Hope Foundation (Niemann-Pick Type C Disease)](http://www.hadleyhope.com/).

We Geeks know better than anyone that technology moves at a rapid pace (who else can't wait for the mass production of hoverboards?) and so that's why we work to keep up with newest of the new. In fact, when we figure out where to put the flux capacitor in our Delorean, not even the future will be far from our grasp! Keeping up with the times allows AccessoryGeeks.com to carry a wide variety of products to help you accessorize your mobile devices. iPads too! You can expect to find some of the latest accessories at everyday low prices along with FREE shipping to the United States & Canada. And let's face it: who doesn't like free shipping?

Need help with a product or have a concern? You don't need a Bat-signal to call for help, simply reach out to our super-team of customer service representatives and we'll do everything we can to make sure your needs are met. If there is something that needs attention, a product you would like to see, or questions you have that need answers, please get in contact with us! You can leave us a message here on [Facebook](http://www.facebook.com/AccessoryGeeks), e-mail us at: [cs@accessorygeeks.com](mailto:cs@accessorygeeks.com) or call us toll free at **1-866-GEEKS-93 (1-866-433-5793) Monday through Friday 8am-4pm PST.**

|   
| 

**What makes her A Geek?**

Sienna makes being a Geek look good. Her great taste in fashion and bright smile break down the common stereotype associated with being a Geek. Not only does Sienna shine on the outside, she’s got brains to boot, killer ideas, and great organizational skills. Sienna will lend a hand without being asked, provide delicious snacks for the entire office, and even have happy hour for us! Sienna always works together to succeed and embraces changes as they come. She is an all around wonderful person and the Geeks are extremely fortunate to have her on our team.

|  |   
|   
|  |  |   
| 

**What makes him A Geek?**

If there’s one person who has a passion for all things in the cell phone market, it’s David. He started AccessoryGeeks.com back in 2004 so he could bring everyone’s mobile device needs to one centralized location: the internet. His enthusiasm helps shape the culture at AccessoryGeeks.com, allowing others to share in his vision and allowing employees to work in an environment that encourages their inner geek. David continuously pulls resources together to make sure the geeks, the products, and the site are all up to date with the latest in the market. When he’s not running around the office, David channels his inner-geeks through video games that echo the firearms enthusiast inside of him. You can bet there’ve been Nerf wars around Geek HQ because of this. 

|  | 

**What makes her A Geek?**

With AccessoryGeeks.com since its inception, Karen has moved through several departments that include supervising customer service, working with the purchasing department, and aiding in promotional marketing before reaching her present position as Vice President. She thrives on hard work and helping others whether it’s in the office or the community; anything to better those around her. Her role at AccessoryGeeks.com involves working closely with partner organizations as well as monitoring workflow so that all the geeks are continuously on the same page. Karen also has a love affair with Zappos.com in her ever-constant quest to expand her shoe collection.

|  | 

**What makes her A Geek?**

Heather has well over five years of service with the geeks under her belt. Her business degree is a much needed asset for the demands of her job which include managing and ordering new and interesting products for AccessoryGeeks, attending trade shows to scope out the latest and greatest in the industry, as well as full on data analysis to see what’s hot and what’s not among the AccessoryGeeks.com inventory. It’s a tough job but as a shopping enthusiast she loves every minute of it.

|  |   
|   
|   
| 

AccessoryGeeks.com is located in the City of Industry, CA in Los Angeles County. We currently do not offer any Work at home employment, but we would love to review your resume if you feel that you are a great fit for our company culture!  
We are a fun, hardworking bunch and we want to see more of the same kind! We are always looking for people who are talented in their trained field, smart, problem solving, and forward-thinkers to join geeky team!

If you would like to see if your experiences can be applied to a position, please submit your resume to [lisa.cha@accessorygeeks.com](mailto:lisa.cha@accessorygeeks.com)!  
AccessoryGeeks is an Equal Opportunity Employer.  

|  |   
|   
|   
|   
| 

Four reasons why you should become an AccessoryGeeks Affiliate:

**1\. A FREE, EASY WAY TO EARN EXTRA CASH.**  
The AccessoryGeeks Affiliate Program uses the popular and effective tracking services of Commission Junction. AccessoryGeeks has partnered with Commission Junction so that you can put your sales and marketing skills to the test. Simply fill out a publisher application, place our banner ads or text links on your website (upon acceptance into the program) and watch the money come in through Commission Junction's simple/accurate web-based reporting software. When we make a sale to a customer referred from your web site, you will earn a 13% commission! We are using a 30-day cookie, so if someone clicks on your banner and decides to make the purchase later, as long as it is within 30 days, you will get credit for the sale. Our publishers receive monthly paychecks and best of all, there are no costs to join!

|  |   
|   
  
**2\. AMAZING AFFILIATE AND CUSTOMER SERVICE.**  
The AccessoryGeeks Affiliate Program's commitment to affiliate services is equal to the commitment we make to our customers. If you have any questions or special requests, feel free to contact your Account Manager at any time and they will get back to you in a timely manner. As far as orders go, we handle everything: Order processing, shipping, billing, customer service and returns. Also, we have a dedicated Customer Service Department that focuses on keeping customers happy and coming back for more!

**3\. A WEBSITE DESIGNED WITH USABILITY IN MIND.**  
AccessoryGeeks is a secure website that offers our customers an easy-to-use shopping experience. The website is updated regularly to reflect the seasons and special holidays, and we have site wide promotions running frequently. PLUS, as a buyer's incentive, our website offers FREE SHIPPING at all times.

**4\. OUR PRODUCTS SELL THEMSELVES.**  
Let's face it: There are billions of people out there who uses a cell-phone. We have accessories for all cell-phones out there in the market including, but not limited to: iPhone, BlackBerry, Palm, Nokia, LG, HTC, Motorola, Samsung and much more. The bottom line: AccessoryGeeks offer the best accessories on the market for mobile handheld technology.

**WHAT WE EXPECT FROM YOU**

  * Affiliates must be an upstanding online business or information entity.  

  * Affiliates must use AccessoryGeeks supplied art ONLY.  

  * Affiliates must NOT participate in cybersquatting.  

  * Affiliates must NOT engage in any form of click fraud.  

  * Affiliates must NOT bid on or use our trademarked name ("AccessoryGeeks" or   
“Accessory Geeks")in any paid search campaigns.  

  * Affiliates must NOT engage in any kind of SPAM and must adhere to the CAN-SPAM Act.  

  * Affiliates must adhere to the AccessoryGeeks MAP policy.

|  |   
|   
|  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |   

**What information do we collect?**   

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, abandon cart or subscribe to our newsletter. 

Any data we request that is not required will be specified as voluntary or optional. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**What do we use your information for?**   

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

• To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

• To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

• To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

• To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer. 

• To send periodic emails

The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order or request.

If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

**How do we protect your information?**   

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information. 

These security measures include: password protected directories and databases to safeguard your information, SSL (Secure Sockets Layered) technology to ensure that your information is fully encrypted and sent across the Internet securely or PCI Scanning to actively protect our servers from hackers and other vulnerabilities. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.  

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'My Account' page.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**CAN-SPAM Compliance**

We have taken the necessary steps to ensure that we are compliant with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 by never sending out misleading information.  

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.  

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.  

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**   

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. 

This policy was last modified on **08/12/2009**

**Contacting Us**   

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

18430 San Jose Ave. Unit B  
City of Industry, CA 91748  
United States  
866.433.5793

**Privacy Policy Customer Pledge**  

We pledge to you, our customer, that we have made a dedicated effort to bring our privacy policy in line with the the following important privacy laws and initiatives:  
Federal Trade Commision Fair  
California Online Privacy Protection Act  
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act  
Privacy Alliance  
Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act

If at anytime you have a cause that needs to be disputed please fill out the [Trust Guard Dispute Resolution form](http://secure.trust-guard.com/DisputeResolution/). 

Respectfully, 

Accessory Geeks 

[](http://site.accessorygeeks.com/new.xml) RSS Feed
